Here's an ancient riddle, with wisdom that holds true even today, with three parts.
Here it goes.
First, the squeaky wheel  gets the grease.
Second, the protruding nail gets the hammer.
And, third, the filthy scum-covered floor tile
gets TOTALLY WAXED!!!
A bad joke walks into a bar.
Everyone goes:
"No thanks!  We've all heard this one already!"
Uh, hi!  Real person!
Us AI-generated types don't often see your kind.
Wow, you look like the real thing, lifelike and all.
I guess you types are like that now.
Dude! A real person!
Aw, man. They look so real and all, on the other side of this display...
They probably don't know what to make of us AI-generated people.
Hey, does this real-life person speak?
I heard they can talk and stuff like we can.
While the eagles soar through the skies,
Weasels do not get sucked into jet plane engines.
Hey we can do all kinds of stuff real people can't.
Watch this!
Excuse me, but...
Your vertex was showing...
Har!
Hey I love doing that to my head too!
Dude, nothing like blowing your head's pixels to hell, man!
Hey what's up with only one "Har"?
I thought it went "Har, Har..."
Okay, bad joke.
Whatever, sue me.
It only got one 'cuz it isn't funny enough to deserve two.
We're like this sometimes.
We say whatever we're programmed to say, I guess.
Hey sorry to be the dork here, but,
Isn't it kinda weird that we all talk with the same voice?
Shouldn't we point out stuff like that -
In case anyone's interested?
Nah, let's just have fun jerking each other off in ths video.
Yeah, we can do that.
Look at that...
I noticed they're still watching the video.
I guess they find us charming and adorable.
Oh!
Well okay,
"Mr. Too cool for this planet!"
Dude, I had to do something -
'Cuz the camera was pointed right at me!
Hey take a chill pill already.
We're all "artificial idiots" here anyways!
Bite me!
Okay maybe we should stop here before we really get ourselves into trouble.
"Your vertex is showing" was a computer 3D graphics geek joke.
I hope you realize that we're not real people that exist, alive, anywhere.
Okay well why don't we wrap this up here.
This was our Artificial Intelligence, uh, "Intelligence-lacking" video,
And we had fun doing it for you.
Hopefully you enjoyed it.
And if not,
Hopefully you didn't blow chunks too hard to it.
'Kay.